HAYK MANVELYAN

I am purposeful, competent, proactive, I like to work hard and strive for growth, I want to develop my knowledge and skills. I worked in the IT-sphere with the 1C program but I want to develop and get professional skills in the sphere of JS and React.

COMPUTER SKILLS

JavaScript

Node JS

React JS

Mongoose

TypeScript

• Git

• HTML / CSS

PORTFOLIO

Project 1

- https://blissful-aryabhata-f7c9b9.netlify.app
- https://github.com/Hayk-HM/CRM-Public.git

Project 1

• https://github.com/Hayk-HM/barcontrol.git

EXPERIENCE

Armenia, Yerevan June 2018 - Present

1C programming and system administrator

MINISO LLC

- Responsible for software
- Problem-solving to improve workflow automation
- Responsible for the correct operation of the server
- · Solving technical problems of employees

Armenia, Yerevan

March 2015 - Present

1C programming and system administrator

CHIMEG LLC

- Responsible for software
- Problem-solving to improve workflow automation
- Responsible for the correct operation of the server
- Solving technical problems of employees

Armenia, Yerevan

July 2013 - September 2015

Assistant to the chief financier

CHIMEG LLC

• Provided the necessary data for the financial report

Armenia, Yerevan

February 2012 - July 2013

Responsible for contacts with foreign partners.

CHIMEG LLC

- Organization of workflow with foreign partners.
- Responsible for the correctness and accuracy of important documents.

Armenia, Yerevan

June 2011 - February 2012

1C operator

CHIMEG LLC

• Responsible for the internal circulation of goods

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

manvelyanhayk@gmail.com

Address

Armenia, Yerevan, Avan-Arinj

Phone

+374 96 02 99 66

Nationality

Armenian

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- · Problem-Solving
- Communication skills
- Inquisitiveness
- Self-motivation
- · Pay attention to details
- Resistant to stressful situations

LANGUAGES

Armenian

Advanced

English

Intermediate. Lezounery Toun 4th cycle

Russian

Advanced

EDUCATION

Armenia, Yerevan

September 2006 - May 2009

Bachelor

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

Computer Engineering

Armenia, Yerevan

September 2002 - May 2006

School

PhysMath School

Armenia, Yerevan

September 2001 - May 2002

School

Usum School

Armenia, Yerevan

September 1997 - May 2001

School

School N:180